The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Since you destroyed my Demon Tower...
I will...
make you pay a hundredfold !
1 hour ago
I can't dodge his Divine Sense attack.
Even if the Celestial Ascension Fruits ignited my killing intent,
their effect is fading.
If I don't severely injure the entity in the black tower,
I'm sure
that I will die.
Then I have to risk it !
Tell me how to use the Blood Soul Pill
in exchange for a chance of survival.
If you don't,
I'll crush my bag of holding before I die
to collapse this space
and trap you in the void forever.
Damn it,
it's you !
Explode !
The backlash of the Celestial Ascension Fruits
is more severe than I imagined...
Even if the black tower was destroyed,
his Origin Soul is still alive.
Only the Ancient Demon will be able to seal him.
I must return to the Sky Demon Country.
He's... still alive ?
Countless years of accumulated energy,
Master's resurrection,
you ruined it all...
Wang Lin !
Some remnants of the fruits are left in my Origin Soul,
I'll be able to use them to block Divine Sense attacks.
There was no enmity between us
but he still attacked me.
As expected, there is no right or wrong
in this cultivation world,
only strength prevails.
Outskirts
of Sky Demon City
Although our promise from 10 years ago was delayed because of my breakthrough,
this matter was extremely important.
I doubt the Ancient Demon will go back on his word.
Wang Lin !
Ling Tianhou ?
No...
This person only looks like him,
his aura is completely different.
Something weird is going on here.
Perhaps I can use this to buy some time.
Ling Tianhou is Da Lou Sword Sect Leader,
how did you obtain his body !?
You're courting death !
Teleporting takes too much time,
I'll have to blast my way through.
Senior Ancient Demon,
how long do you intend to watch !?
You...
are going to die !
You're 10 years late
and still dare to order me around ?
I beg Senior for help.
Bei Luo,
stay out of this !
This is my territory,
you have no right to order me.
Lend me your blood.
Bei Luo...
Do you dare to stop me ?
I would've stopped if the Ancient Devil had come.
But you are just one of the nine Scattered Devils of the Ancient Devil.
Who do you think you are !?
Senior,
10 years ago...
Shut up !
Heal yourself.
Their spells
are somewhat similar to Ancient God spells.
The Ancient Demon, Ancient Devil, and Ancient God clans
all originate from the Ancient Order.
This is an opportunity for you to comprehend their Dao.
Watch carefully.
Ancient Gods are neither Demon nor Devil.
In their palms lies the power to shatter space.
This fight between the Ancient Demon and the Scattered Devil
has allowed me to understand some Ancient God spells.
The benefits for my original body
are inestimable.
3 days later
I finally finished refining
the 4 drops of Celestial Wine.
But this fight between the Ancient Demon and the Scattered Devil
is very strange.
The Ancient Demon seems to be hitting lethal strikes each time
but in reality, he's holding back.
Could he...
be showing him mercy ?
Bei Luo,
is fighting me to the death over an ant
worth it ?
I don't need
to explain to you why I do it.
You fool !
Master won't let you off !
So he is wary of the Ancient Devil.
But if this mad dog escapes,
he'll likely come back for me to the ends of the world.
Since there's no way to resolve this matter peacefully anymore,
I must act thoroughly.
Billion-Soul Flag
enter the Underworld River !
Xu Liguo !
Th...This is...
M...Master...
If I can help Master slay this Devil,
it's worth it !
Now...
I'll play all my cards
to eradicate your soul !
Although I, Wang Lin, am weak,
I'm not someone you can mess with !
As long as you stay behind him,
he'll have endless fuel.
Yet, you dare to come to me yourself ?
You're courting death !
You nearly killed me before
and forced me to flee for 3000 li !
I will make you pay
blood for blood !
With your level of cultivation,
what can you do to me !?
This is...
a chaotic power blending Divine Sense and his comprehension of the Dao  !
My Divine Sense is unstable
and I've lost the Demon Tower.
I shouldn't fight any longer.
Although my body was destroyed,
I can always make a comeback
as long as the armor remains.
He knows he can't kill the Scattered Devil.
What is he trying to do ?
You won't
be able to escape !
Without the Celestial Ascension Fruits,
you can't withstand even a wisp of my devil soul !
Who told you
that my Celestial Ascension Fruits
are all used up ?
Do you think you can fight me
with your meager comprehension of the Dao !?
It's just some remnants !
So what if they blocked my devil soul once ?
Since you're determined to die,
then even if
I have to sacrifice some of my cultivation,
I will possess you for sure !
The final move
relies on
me not being alone.
Well played, Wang Lin.
You used yourself as bait
to trap the Scattered Devil within your Origin Soul
and force me to intervene.
If I help you,
I will fulfill your wish.
If I don't help you,
these 3 days of fighting
would've been in vain.
Since you predicted I would help,
then this is your good fortune.
Cloud Sky Sect
Planet Suzaku
Is he the one
from that legend ?
He entered the Celestial Realm,
beat Red Butterfly,
fought Qian Feng.
All by himself,
he shook the entire planet Suzaku.
Then why didn't he become the Suzaku ?
That's the highest position !
His path
lies beyond the sea of stars.
The rain has stopped.
May he protect our clan and grant us peace and prosperity.
These candles
are the lights we send for him.
Wang Lin's
Sea of Consciousness
After months of cultivating,
I finally stabilized my Ascendant cultivation.
I can't fully refine this Devil for now
but I can already suppress him
with the help of the Ancient Demon.
When the time comes,
I can refine him into my second Origin Soul.
As for this demon armor...
Dragon Pool
Sky Demon Country
If I use the Demonic Finger with this armor,
it would be even stronger than the Underworld River.
Are you
leaving already ?
The Ancient Demon has helped me multiple times
at a considerable cost.
If I leave now,
he'll think I'm abandoning him.
Senior has helped me 3 times,
I will remember it.
The reason I'm leaving
is precisely to fulfill our agreement.
But before that,
I would like to ask Senior's help with something.
Speak...
Can senior help me find an old friend ?
His Divine Sense is on this pagoda.
There's no such Sword Spirit in the Sky Demon Country.
If you want me to search the entire Demon Spirit Land,
you must first retrieve a Demon Spirit for me.
Agreed.
This person is definitely connected to Sword Saint Ling Tianhou.
Keeping him could come in use later.
Two more things.
First,
I want this person.
Second,
I want to enter the Ancient Demon inheritance
to refine my spells.
I can give you the person
but for the Ancient Demon inheritance...
If within 100 years,
you can obtain a Demon Spirit,
then we'll discuss it.
Okay.
But with just my strength,
it will be difficult.
From now on,
you are my Sky Demon Envoy.
Your identity is higher than the Demon Emperor.
My Sky Demon Country will officially wage war to the Fire Demon Country.
You will use this opportunity
to approach the Fire Demon Spirit.
I will fulfill my mission
within 100 years.
After the Blood Soul Pill absorbs a trace of Divine Sense and blood, it also activates another ability for a short period of time. At the moment of death, anything that is linked to the Origin Soul will be merged with the void. After one is resurrected, they can use the power of their soul and blood to retrieve the items stored in the void.
That small glimpse at planet Suzaku is a whole chapter in the novel where we learn that Zhou Ru has become some kind of princess of planet Suzaku and has reached Core Formation. She is protected by Chi Hu the new Patriarch of the Giant Demon Clan, Yunque Zi of the Forsaken Immortal Clan, Zhou Wutai the Suzaku and Little White the tiger.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.